Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Aqua Pearl
Episode 29
No response.
I must protect the Aqua Pearl.
I won’t let anyone touch it.
Xiao Mei, what’s wrong?
What?
Don’t move.
Open.
I was wondering when Dr. Mei had acquired a daughter.
…and she was so determined to protect you.
So, you are the key.
Let her go!
Don’t do anything rash.
Otherwise, I can’t guarantee what might happen to her.
How despicable.
As long as I possess it,
I’ll have an endless supply of water.
Here, you take over.
Yes.
Oh no…
My hand…it feels so heavy.
I’ll go get the Aqua Pearl.
Xiao Mei
No one is going to take the Aqua Pearl from me.
It’s so heavy.
The Aqua Pearl is mine.
Why can’t I see Guangzong anywhere?
Guangzong and the others must have slipped into the cave.
Trust Weslie and the others.
I can’t hold on much longer.
Let me handle it.
I’ll blast a path through here.
Wait, your shells are too powerful.
If an explosion happens here,
we’ll be the ones who get hurt first.
So, what can we do?
I have an idea.
ID 0420.
I have transformed you into a robot that guards the Aqua Pearl.
Remember, your mission is to guard the Aqua Pearl.
I…I am a robot.
Xiao Mei.
Xiao Mei, you aren’t a robot at all.
You are my daughter.
You
are simply yourself.
I am…
Shut up.
From now on,
you must live for yourself.
Remember, you have only one mission.
Xiao Mei!
Protect the Aqua Pearl well.
No one but me is allowed to touch it.
Protect the Aqua Pearl.
Xiao Mei.
What’s going on?
How did it suddenly become so powerful?
Xiao Mei.
My Aqua Pearl…
Aqua…Pearl
Xiao Mei
Protect the Aqua Pearl
Wake up
Xiao Mei
Are you okay?
We can’t let them get the Aqua Pearl!
Quick, get it back!
But you got hurt because of the Aqua Pearl.
Is it worth it?
We’ve come this far
How could I give up?
I’m taking this
all just for the sake of your better lives.
But now…
I’m completely out of options.
How about I get that one?
Really?
I’m so happy!
Here’s the plan:
Once you grab it, I’ll pull you out with a stick.
Okay, I’m going to get the Aqua Pearl now.
I’m counting on you.
I’m going to get this Aqua Pearl.
I know you won’t let me down.
I can do this.
I’m here to help you.
Hurry, hurry!
Save me!
Take anything of value.
Come back!
Don’t leave me behind!
Someone, save me!
I’m here.
Check out these gauntlets I just upgraded with those machine parts.
Jay?
Why can’t I get in touch with anyone?
Everyone has lost contact.
Could it be that they…
ran into danger?
My poor kids.
Mr. Slowy, we’re back.
I’m glad you’re back.
By the way, did you get the fragments?
We ran into a few surprises,
but we got the fragments.
Well done.
I need to study these fragments carefully.
It’s you.
Don’t speak. I’ll bandage that for you.
To think that the two of us, usually so sharp,
actually got tricked by you.
A villain as wicked as you
must be punished.
You only got tricked because you were naïve.
The ones with the problem
are you.
Attack!
Explode!
I will protect Aqua Pearl.
Weslie.
You heinous villain
Surrender immediately
You are Xiao Mei
I am 0420
You are definitely not a robot
Do you remember the time we spent together?
The desert flower you picked for me
When you had a fever and leaned on my arm
When you leaned on me out of fear
The final moment we shared with Big Sister
I am Xiao Mei
Xiao Mei
I’m sorry for the trouble I’ve caused you all.
It’s a relief that you’re okay.
Don’t even think about hurting them again.
I’ve been wondering…
If the two fragments were fused together,
just how much power would that generate?
This fragment holds so much energy;
it absolutely must not fall into the wrong hands.
What?
To be continued